<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vishu Mathana</string>
    <string name="step_1">This is Vishu Mathana, a Freelance Graphic Designer, and writer basically from Kurukshetra, Haryana. I have been part of music industry since 2012 and designed more than 10,000 official posters. I have also worked with some of the renowned faces in the same industry\n\n</string>
    <string name="step_2">Surprisingly, I too have an interesting story about my dream city "Bombay". Bombay, being the hub of music and film industry, had always been my dream place to work.\n\n</string>
    <string name="step_3">This turned into reality when I designed Salman Khan\'s poster for his movie "Prem Ratan Dhan Payo" and the same he posted on his Instagram account for the special appreciation. Apart from this, My own designed poster of Movie "Jai Ho" got top most rank on internet and simultaneously got viral in media. I also won the contest on Twitter and certainly it added another feather to my cap when I got chance to see the trailer of movie, "Kick" in Bombay with "Salman Khan." Moreover, I won a contest as well which is organised by "Being Human".\n\n</string>
    <string name="step_4">1st March 2021 is the day when my dream comes true and my composed work came out in the structure of book named as “Sabkuchh”.\n\n</string>
    <string name="step_5">Our entire life revolves around the words. But some words combined with emotions, have potential to make us laugh and cry all together. They leave such imprints that even cannot be healed or erased by time. Occasionally, the words which seem so simple could be quite intricate at the same time, as sometimes the foundation of the whole life is based on these words. Keeping this all in mind, the name of what is made with all the feelings and eternal love is "Sabkuchh".\n\n</string>
    <string name="step_6">If you just believe its nothing, but if it is understood profoundly, it is everything.\n\n</string>

    <string name="step_7">Thanks to all for believing in me and always giving the best possible response to my work. I assure you all to keep this faith intact forever. Because working as a Graphic Designer is not only my profession but passion..!</string>
    <string name="step_8">Our entire life revolves around the words. But some words combined with emotions, have potential to make us laugh and cry all together. They leave such imprints that even cannot be healed or erased by time. Occasionally, the words which seem so simple could be quite intricate at the same time, as sometimes the foundation of the whole life is based on these words.Keeping this all in mind, the name of what is made with all the feelings and eternal love is "Sabkuchh". If you just believe its nothing, but if it is understood profoundly, it is everything.</string>

    <string name="book_about">Our entire life revolves around the words. But some words combined with emotions, have potential to make us laugh and cry all together. They leave such imprints that even cannot be healed or erased by time. Occasionally, the words which seem so simple could be quite intricate at the same time, as sometimes the foundation of the whole life is based on these words. Keeping this all in mind, the name of what is made with all the feelings and eternal love is "Sabkuchh"</string>

    <string-array name="home_menus">
        <item>ABOUT ME</item>
        <item>MY BOOK</item>
        <item>SONG POSTERS</item>
        <item>EVENT FLYERS</item>
        <item>DIGITAL FLYERS</item>
        <item>BUSINESS FLYERS</item>
        <item>LOGO DESIGN</item>
        <item>DIGITAL PAINTING</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
